（忆往昔）
血印不会让宿主轻易死去
The mark of cain never lets its host die easy.
只不过是个诅咒 是可以去掉的
It's just a curse. It can be removed.
这是炼狱
This is purgatory.
在那里 有种感觉
There was something about being there.
大部分时候是上下左右受敌
Most days felt like 360-degree combat.
觉得纯粹
It felt pure.
卡思伯特·辛克莱尔 被封为「咒文大师」
Cuthbert Sinclair. He was named "Master of spells."
他的作为变得有些疯狂了
His work got a little crazy.
领导层说他「怪异」「不负责任」
The leadership called it "Eccentric and irresponsible."
我们完了
We're done.
那么你选了温家兄弟
So you're choosing the Winchesters.
我选择我
I'm choosing me.
《诅咒之书》是一本咒语书
"The book of the damned" is a spell book.
是用来创造或解开所有诅咒的
for creating or undoing any kind of damnation there is.
我们如果能翻译过来
We translate this thing,
我觉得就能把你的该隐血印去掉 迪恩
I think we can get the Mark of Cain off you, Dean.
我不信任你 但我需要帮助
I don't trust you, but I need help.
我需要把该隐血印从我哥哥身上弄掉
I need the mark of Cain off of my brother.
而我觉得你能破解这本书
Something tells me you can crack this book.
唯一的问题是…
The only question is,
- 你会帮我吗 - 我们谈谈条件吧
- Will you help me? - Shall we discuss terms?
（密苏里州 圣路易斯）
- 滚开 - 我的节目刚开始
- Get lost. - My show just started.
你房间里有唱片机
You have a record player in your room.
- 老爸的扬声器更好 - 那又怎样
- Dad's speakers are better. - Tough luck.
得把衣服洗上 工人终于走了
I need the laundry started. The workmen have finally left.
而我要忙着准备晚饭
for the day, and I have my hands full with dinner.
少拿女权跟我说事
And please, none of your Betty Friedan stuff.
这不公平
It's not fair.
你总让我做家务
Look, I always get stuck with the hard chores.
就因为我是女孩
just 'cause I'm the girl.
那又怎样
Yeah? Well, tough luck.
房子很不错 泰德
The house is great, Ted.
还有待修缮 但真的很不错
It's a bit of a fixer, but it's a real beaut.
前几年一直受产权纠纷困扰
It was caught in some ownership muddle for years.
但终于出售了 我立刻就买下了
But finally hit the market, and I leapt.
别在下面待一整天
Don't spend all day down there!
妈妈
Mom?
爸爸 妈妈呢
Dad, where's mom?
妈妈
Mom?
布拉德
Brad?
妈妈
Mom?
Mom!
都会没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.
都没事的
Everything's…
没事的
Gonna be just fine.
[邪恶力量 第10季第19集]
只有一件事
There's only one thing.
是你可以帮我做
you could possibly do for me.
而我自己却暂时做不到的
that I can't, at least presently, do for myself.
杀了我儿子
Kill my son.
他知道我要杀他
He's expecting it from me.
已经让他讨厌的手下提高警惕了
Already has his stinking minions on high alert.
如果你在想 一个母亲怎么会到
And if you're wondering how a mother can get to the point.
- 想害死亲生子的地步… - 我真没想
- of wanting her own son… - No, I'm really not.
我做
I'll do it.
我替你杀了克劳力
I'll kill Crowley.
重要的事先说
First things first…
你能读懂这本书吗
Can you read the book?
当然了
Of course I can.
我可能是当今在世
I'm likely the only witch alive.
唯一能理解这么古老的黑魔法的女巫了
who can understand such old, dark magic.
只是目前这样子读不懂
Just not in its present form.
酒水我请
Drink's on me.
哪都别想去 伙计
You're not going anywhere, pal.
我是你的死敌
I'm your mortal enemy.
我曾试图杀你和你哥哥
I've tried to kill you and your brother…
试图杀你哥还是上个月的事
Your brother as recently as last month.
如果不是走投无路 你才不会来找我
You wouldn't have come to me if I wasn't your last resort.
你已经没别的办法了
You're desperate.
别再假装不是这样了
You can stop pretending you're not.
真没礼貌
So rude.
（迪恩 在塔尔萨突袭一个巢穴 要来自便）
好了 书现在这样我是读不懂
Now…I can't read the book in its present form,
但有个人读得懂
But there is someone who could.
娜迪娅 大巫师团的女巫
Nadya. Grand coven witch.
我在哪能找到她
Where do I find her?
找不到 她已经死了
You don't. She's dead.
早死了
Long ago.
因为毕生的工作被杀了
Murdered for her life's work.
但她的解码公式 她的法典
Her decryption formulas, her codex…
这个你是找得到的
That you can find.
把娜迪娅的法典拿来给我
Bring me Nadya's codex, and I'll…
我马上就能破解密文
break this text right open.
把破咒办法告诉你
and give you your cure.
我去哪找
Where do I look?
如果我是你 就从家里找起
If I were you, I'd start at home.
你以为是谁杀了娜迪娅
Who do you think murdered Nadya.
偷了她的法典啊
and stole the codex in the first place?
记录者
The men of letters.
中奖
Jackpot.
迪恩
Dean!
这怎么回事
What happened? What is this?
可不是
I know, right?
六个吸血鬼 我一人干掉
Six vamps. Solo.
绝对打破个人最好成绩了
I think that's gotta be a personal best.
- 你就不能等等吗 - 等什么
- You couldn't have waited?! - For what?
- 等什么 - 拜托
- For what? - Oh, come on, man.
我能应付得来 我应付过来了
I can handle it. I did handle it.
- 万一你应付不来呢 - 这不是没事吗
- What if you couldn't? - But I did.
都干完了
It's done.
得了 只有这样我才能消除紧张
Come on, man. It's the only way I can take the edge off.
抱歉了 我并不是总喜欢等你
I'm sorry. I don't always like to wait around for you,
尤其你还老那么看我
Especially with you looking at me like that all the time.
- 怎么看你了 - 那样
- Look at you like what? - Like that.
好像我是得了病的疯狂杀人犬
Like I'm some sort of a-a-a diseased killer puppy.
告诉你
You know what, man?
我一身臭汗和吸血鬼血
I'm sweaty and I'm covered in vamp juice.
我们能回头再说吗
Can we just talk about this later?
我想赶紧回地堡 喝点小酒
I'd like to get back to the bunker, get my buzz on,
然后
and, uh, you know,
看《生死时速2 怒海红颜》睡过去
Pass out watching "Speed 2: cruise control."
没事了吧
We cool?
没事
Cool.
（记录者会议纪要 56年5月16日 另见 开除卡思伯特·辛克莱尔）
会议正式召开
Please, let come to order.
记录者会议纪要
Men of letters meeting minutes…
1956年5月16日
May 16, 1956.
讨论开除卡思伯特·辛克莱尔
On the matter of Cuthbert Sinclair expulsion.
这已经不是你的初犯了 卡思伯特
This is hardly your first offence, Cuthbert.
你任职期间
You've been cited for disciplinary infractions.
曾七次违反纪律
seven times in the course of your tenure.
你这个施了法术的地下室
This…enchanted vault of yours,
这个
this…
「维特箱」
"Werther box."
被施以强效保护咒 以至于理论上能达到…
A warding so potent it achieves a theoretical rate of…
你的原话是 「98%的致死率」
in your own words, "98% lethality."
必须采取极端手段
Extreme measures were warranted.
巫师团为夺回法典不择手段
The coven's desperate to get the codex back.
维特箱能保护好法典
The werther box works.
太过头了吧
All too well, I'd say.
你秘密行动
Working in secret,
不受监管启动这个项目
embarking on this project without oversight…
你使得两名记录者
You left two fellow men of letters vulnerable.
被你强大的魔法所伤
to your most potent magics.
弗莱彻和马丁纳兹都是声誉很好的成员
Fletcher and Martinez were members in good standing.
弗莱彻试图打开箱子 两小时内就死了
Fletcher chanced upon the box and died in two hours.
马丁纳兹英勇地企图中止魔法
Martinez heroically tried to shut it down.
却死在箱子旁边的地上
We found him dead on the floor beside the box,
手腕被割开
his wrists cut.
我已经为这起意外道过歉了
I already apologized for that accident.
我不会再道一次了
I refuse to do so again.
你们为什么目光这么狭隘
Why are you all so small-minded?
我们被带来这里 是为成就伟业
We were brought here to do great things.
是为冒险
To take risks,
是为把这世界上的怪物赶尽杀绝
to bring the fight to the monsters of this world…
但是 你们全部
And yet, to a man,
选择躲在这些书堆里
you choose instead to moulder in these stacks.
你们不是男人 你们不配做男人
You are not men. You are not men.
你们就是一群图书管理员而已
You're librarians. Nothing more.
我们对
Before we rule.
如何处置你做出裁决前
on what is to be done with you,
我要再给你一次争取宽大的机会
I'm prepared to give you a chance to secure our leniency.
告诉我们如何中止魔法
Tell us how to shut it down.
箱子和法典还在圣路易斯
The box is still in St. Louis with the codex.
依然是个威胁
It's still a danger.
我告诉你你该怎么发挥你的宽大吧 马卡姆
Let me tell you what you can do with your leniency, Markham.
告诉你们
You know,
我早就明白你们的意思了
I saw the writing on the wall.
我就知道你们这群胆小鬼会中止项目
I knew you cowards would shut this project down,
所以我才把它打造成那样
which is why I built it the way I did.
想中止维特只有一个办法
There is only one way to silence the Werther for good.
这么说吧 马丁纳兹的思路是正确的
Let's just say Martinez was on the right track.
我看你们根本没这个胆子
I doubt you lot have the guts,
不过尽管拼死一试吧
but you're welcome to die trying.
马卡姆 要我们继续尝试吗
Markham, would you have us keep trying?
就地埋葬并守护箱子
The box is to be interred and guarded where it stands,
永不得打开
in perpetuity.
埋好
Bury it.
（圣路易斯分部 密苏里州 圣路易斯 德菲街2111号）
有点早了吧
It's a bit early.
我都三百多岁了
I'm over 300 years old.
想早起都不行
Beauty sleep isn't optional.
我一直在调查我们之前说的那事
I've been looking into the, uh, thing we discussed.
我有所发现
So I got a lead,
但它受到了厉害的咒语保护
but it's guarded by a violent enchantment.
我需要一个咒语
I need a spell to…
来破解咒语
break the spell.
卡比利恩符咒
The Cabirian invocation.
很容易得到 什么咒都能破解
Easy to obtain. Good all-purpose disenchantment.
- 很好 多谢 - 不过
- Great. Thanks. - Uh, but…
不建议外行人使用
It's not recommended for amateurs.
如果没有经验
In inexperienced hands,
操作符咒可能会失控
the invocation has a way of fizzling out.
我可以去啊
I could come.
你或许用得上我
You might need me.
我宁可碰运气 谢了
I'll take my chances. Thanks.
别想了
Bad idea.
- 我能解释的 - 省省吧
- I-I can explain. - Yeah, don't bother.
给你三个选择
You got three choices…
被捕
Get arrested,
被阉 滚蛋
get your bits blown off, or get back.
嗯 好吧 我还是走吧
Yeah, all right. I think I'll, uh, think get back.
- 抱歉 - 这还差不多
- Sorry. - Attaboy.
好啊 萨姆
Hey ya, Sammy.
案子进展如何
How's the case?
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
看来我是来拯救你的蛋蛋的呢
Well, it looks like I, uh, I'm here to save your sac.
你说得对 好吗
Look, you were right. Okay?
我不该像之前那样单独行动的
I shouldn't have gone off solo like I did.
是我犯蠢
It was stupid.
还有呢
And?
还自私 很混蛋
And selfish. It was a douche move.
但如果你自己来查案 就为了教训我
If you're doing this case by yourself to teach me a lesson,
没必要的 好吗
you don't have to, okay?
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
我
I, uh…
拓印了你的笔记本
Took an etching off your notepad.
于是决定来看看圣路易斯自杀之屋
Then I decided to take a crack at the, uh, St. Louis suicide house.
你知道这里啊
So you know about it?
谷歌上查了个大概
I got the basics from google.
一家搬进长期闲置的房子
The family moves into a long-vacant house.
一周后
Uh, one week later,
三人自杀
three of 'em dead by their own hands.
除了女儿 全家灭门
Whole family wiped out except for the daughter,
而房子还在她名下
which the house is still under her name.
我猜刚刚差点阉了你的应该就是她了
I'm figuring she's the one who nearly unmanned you back there.
但我不明白的是
But see, here's what I don't get.
悬案是一回事
I mean, a cold case is one thing, but…
这案子都多老了
this is subzero.
而且也没什么跟我们相关的东西
I mean, there's nothing even in our wheelhouse,
除非你知道什么我不知道的
unless you know something I don't.
是啊
Yeah.
这栋长期闲置的房子
That "long-vacant home"
曾是记录者一个分部的房子
used to be a men of letters chapter house.
记得马格纳斯吗
Remember Magnus?
那个差点把我做成标本的
You mean the dickwad ex-men of letters.
混蛋前记录者吗 记得
that tried to make a zoo exhibit out of me? Yeah.
他被开除之前 建了一个维特箱
Before he was expelled, he built werther,
是一个魔法箱子 有致命的警报系统
a magical box with a deadly alarm system.
维特箱就埋在那栋房子里
Werther is buried somewhere in that house.
本该是该有人守卫的
It was supposed to have been guarded,
但我猜阿比顿58年
but I'm guessing that plan went out the window.
杀了所有人后就没人来守了
when Abaddon massacred the entire membership in '58.
然后房子一直闲置
And then the house stayed in limbo.
直到被一个幸运的家庭买下
until some lucky family bought it.
维特箱是个定时炸弹
Werther's a time bomb.
得想办法拆除它
and it needs to be defused.
这不仅与我们有关
Not only is this in our wheelhouse,
更是我们的责任
it's our responsibility.
我们的责任
Our responsibility?
我们是记录者
We're men of letters.
这是我们的遗产
It's our legacy.
既然你说是案子
Well, hey, if you say this is a case…
那就算我一个
I'm in.
如果你不介意的话
if you'll have me.
我怎么说的
What did I say?!
我…
I…
你不是
You're not…
有个人想…
Fella tried to…
你想干什么
What do you want?
你看见他了
You saw him?
你看见了吧
Oh, tell me you did.
抱歉 我叫德怀特·特维利
I'm sorry, but my name is… is Dwight Twilley.
我是邻里联防队的
I'm with the neighborhood watch.
我们在调查几起最近的入室事件
We're… we're looking into a few recent break-ins.
如果你看见那人了
And if you saw the guy and you.
能跟我描述一下的话
… y-you could give a description,
那就太棒了
it would be mighty helpful.
能占用您一点时间吗
If I could… if I could just have a minute of your… time?
高个 白人
Tall white fella.
头发挺好看
Pretty hair.
你家不错啊
It's a nice house you have here, uh…
苏茜
Suzie.
苏茜 一个人住吗
Suzie. You live alone?
只有我和嘉斯
Just me and Gus.
嘉斯
Gus?
一个人住这么大的房子啊
So all alone in this big house, huh?
一定很孤单吧 就算有嘉斯
Must get lonely, even with, uh, Gus.
嗯 我习惯了一个人
Yeah, well, I'm used to alone.
不了 谢谢
No, no. I'm fine, thanks.
我一个人住很久了 自从…
Been alone here since, uh…
80年代吧
'80?
我一家人死后
After my family died,
我姨妈保琳曾搬进来
my aunt Pauline moved in.
她照顾我 养了我几年
She took care of me, raised me for a few years.
后来
Then, well…
发生了什么事
So, uh, what… what happened?
你姨妈
To your aunt?
这个嘛
Well…
我叫她别去地下室的
I told her not to go in the basement.
不能进地下室啊
No one goes in the basement.
地下室里有什么 苏茜
What's in the basement, Suzie?
女士 你没事吧
Ma'am, you okay?
苏茜
Suzie.
我的社交能力虽然生疏了 但我不傻
My social skills may be rusty, but I'm no idiot.
已经几个月没人按过我的门铃了
Doorbell hasn't rung in months,
然后一小时内就来了两个人
and two visitors in one hour?
一个试图闯入
One breaking in,
另一个来问我各种问题…
and the other asking all sorts of q-questions about…
我说了 我是邻里联防队的
I told you, I was from the neighborhood watch. I…
嗯 邻里联防队 得了吧
Yeah, yeah, neighborhood watch. Right.
你看过这个家了吗
Boy, you seen this house?
这里只有一样东西值得偷
There's only one thing in here worth gettin' at,
而且绝对不是我
and it sure as hell ain't me.
- 好吧 - 你是为箱子而来
- Okay. - You came for the box.
[咒语]
不管是谁把那破玩意留在了下面
Whoever left that godforsaken thing down there…
我知道总有一日会有人来取
I knew someday, someone would come for it.
我发誓绝不让他们得逞
I swore never to let that happen.
他就在楼下 是吗
He's downstairs, isn't… isn't he?
他是我弟弟 我们是来帮你的
He's my brother. And we're here to help you.
你叫他上来
You call him up here.
快点
Now!
叫他上来
You call him up here!
- 快点 - 好吧 萨姆
- Now! - Okay. Sam!
萨姆
Sammy!
[咒语]
她叫你马上上来
She wants you up here now!
不 不
No. No!
出去
Get out!
快出去
出去 出去
Out! Out!
- 你们这些混蛋 - 好吧
- You bastards! - Okay. Okay.
你们把它放出来了
You let it out!
迪恩
Dean!
别激动
Take it easy.
你知道你做了什么吗
You have any idea what you've done?!
把枪放下 我们好商量
Put the gun down. We can talk about this, okay?
那是什么
What's that?
苏茜 想我了吗
Hey, Suzie. You miss me?
天呐
Oh, my god.
- 她怎么了 - 我不知道
- What's wrong with her? - I don't know.
别过来
Stay back.
Stay back!
走
Go.
拜托 苏茜 就这么对待家人啊
Come on, Suze. That any way to treat your family?
你好啊 苏茜
Hello, Suzie.
你做了什么
What did you do, huh?
你没有计划 毫无防备
You don't have a plan. You don't have a defense.
不
No.
是你害了我们
You did this to us.
是你把它放出来了
You let it out.
你睡着了 我们却死了
We died while you slept.
不
No!
- 苏茜 - 不
- Suzie! - No!
苏茜
Suzie?
求你们 够了 住口
Please! No! Stop!
别说了
Stop!
苏茜
Suzie!
苏茜 让我进去 我能帮你
Suzie, let me in! I can help you!
- 苏茜 那是幻觉 - 你不用难过
- Suzie, it's not real! - You don't have to be sad.
也不用一个人待着
And you don't have to be alone.
苏茜 求你
Suzie, please!
再也不用了
Not anymore.
苏茜 让我进去 我能帮你
Suzie! Hey, let me in. I can help you, okay?
- 求你们 别说了 - 苏茜
- Oh, please, no. - Suzie?!
迪恩
Dean!
萨姆
Sam?!
苏茜
Suzie?!
该死
Crap.
在这个家里活了40年
Survived 40 years in this house,
一直锁住那东西
keeping that thing on lockdown,
结果你个傻瓜一来
and one visit from a putz like you…
很抱歉 真对不起
I'm sorry, okay? I'm so sorry.
抱歉对我有个屁用
Lot of good "sorry" does me.
看看我
Look at me.
看看我啊
Look…at…me.
她在那儿呢
There she is.
第一个因你错误的任务而死的人
First casualty of your misguided mission.
不过死个人对你来说又如何呢
But what's another human life to you?
做什么都值得
Anything's worth it,
只要你俩能活下来就行
as long as you two make it out alive.
你的搜寻怎么样了
And how's that search going?
接近找到解决办法了吗
Any closer to a cure?
这是幻觉
This isn't real.
你是个幻觉
You're not real.
你觉得迪恩不听话 鲁莽
You think Dean's the wild card, the loose cannon.
但你还不明白吗
But don't you see?
跟女巫做交易
Making deals with witches,
在楼下打开潘多拉之盒
opening pandora's box down there?
你才是鲁莽的那个
You're the reckless one.
为了留住你那个没救的哥哥
You'll do anything to keep clinging to.
你什么都肯做
that doomed brother of yours.
还要死多少人 萨姆
How many more will die, Sammy?
你也明白 必须有人阻止你
You know it. You have to be stopped!
只有你自己能阻止你
And the only one who can stop you is you!
动手吧 萨姆
Do it, Sammy!
永远结束这场闹剧
End this farce once and for all!
[咒语]
我就说你会需要我
Told you you'd need me.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
跟我救你的方式一样
Same way I just saved you…
靠魔法
Magic.
我就觉得你可能招架不来
Had a feeling you might be in over your head.
你不能待在这里
Yeah, well, you can't be here.
如果迪恩看到你了
If Dean sees you…
迪恩
Dean?
萨姆
Sam?
迪恩
Dean?
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
好啊 伙计
Hey, chief.
不不 不可能是你
No. No, it can't be you.
醒醒
Wake up!
迪恩 不管你看见了什么 都不是真的
Dean, whatever you're seeing, it's not real!
对他来说很真实
Real enough to him.
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
他看不到我的 萨姆
He can't see me, Sam.
他已经深陷幻境了
Yeah, he's too far gone.
能唤醒他吗
Can you wake him up?
我的驱散咒只够一个人的
I only brought enough dispelling magic for one.
谁叫你不告诉我不止我们俩
Maybe if you'd told me we'd have company…
- 没有什么「我们」 - 好吧
- There is no "we." - Fine.
那你自己解决吧
Take this all on by yourself.
不过现在情况对你很不利哦
But the odds are totally stacked against you.
你不是真的
You're not real.
咒语的法力很强大啊
Oh, the spell's got its hooks in deep.
如果想让他醒过来
If you want him woken up…
就得从根源破除咒语
you're gonna have to rip this enchantment out by the root.
箱子
The box.
只要能破解保险机制
If we can figure out the fail-safe,
就能解除咒语 找到法典
we can break the spell and get the codex.
幻觉让苏茜自尽而亡
Suzie's hallucinations drove her to suicide.
她的家人也是
Same thing happened to her family.
维特的幻觉刚刚差点也害死我
Werther's illusions tried to do the same thing to me.
所以呢
And so?
所以迪恩这样 我不能丢下他一人
So I can't leave Dean alone like this.
那么
Well, then…
我们得把这个帅小伙绑起来了
we'll just have to tie up the bonny lad.
肯定好玩
Could be fun.
别这样 迪恩 你还打算这样多久
Come on, Dean. How long you gonna keep this up?
不跟我说话吗
The silent treatment for me?
咱们有好多话要聊呢
We got so much to catch up on.
见到你真好 真的
Hey, look, it's good to see you, okay? It is.
但我已经说了 你不是本尼
But like I said, you ain't Benny.
不是吗
I'm not?
- 该死 - 我也挺郁闷的
- Well, shoot. - Hey, I'm bummed out, too,
但你是虚构的
But you are just a figment, okay?
你是我大脑的潜意识产生的幻觉
You're … you're subconscious junk my brain's throwing up.
阻碍我回到现实中去
to distract me from getting back to reality.
虚构 幻觉
"Figment"? "Junk"?
我有点受伤了
Well, I'll try not to be offended.
为什么不相信我呢
Why not trust me?
我之前就帮你逃离过这里
I've gotten you outta here before.
再说了 如果我是你潜意识的幻觉
Besides, if all I am is your "subconscious junk, "
我又怎么会欺骗你呢
well, then how can I lead you wrong?
瞧啊
Well, how about that?
绕了一圈
A perfect circle.
别看我啊 伙计
Don't look at me, chief.
是你自己选的路
You chose the way.
这里 上面刻着一些铭文
Here it is. There's some kind of inscription.
是草书 但已经被磨得看不清了
It's some kind of cursive, but the light source has dimmed.
我知道我之前对你们记录者评价不高
I know what I've said about your kind,
但打造了这个箱子的人
but… the man who came up with this?
这精美的做工
The craftsmanship of the box,
这怨毒的咒语
the sadism of the spellwork…
真是…
it's all so…
太美太巴洛克了
deliciously baroque.
好吧 快点
All right, come on.
[咒语]
太诡异了
Well, now that is just creepy.
本尼 不管你是什么 我得出去
Benny … whoever you are … I need to get out of here.
你「得」出去 不代表你想出去 是吧
"Need" and "want" are two different things, ain't they?
这只是幻境 是吧
It's all a figment, right?
我和你 左和右
You, me, left, right.
但无论你选择哪条路
But no matter which way you turn,
最后还是来到这里
you keep ending up here.
不仅得想
You gotta wonder …
为什么是这种幻境
why this figment?
为什么是这里
Why this place?
你什么意思
What are you saying?
不过是你已经知道的
Nothing you don't already know.
你自己想待在这儿
This is where you wanna be …
你的快乐天堂
your happy place.
你并不真的想离开
And you don't really wanna leave.
[拉丁文]
想要让箱子失效
"To silence the box…"
[拉丁文]
要止其渴
"Slake its thirst…"
[拉丁文]
以我同族人之血
"With…the blood of our own."
就这样吗
That's it?
同族人之血 什么东西
"The blood of its own…" what?
以我同族人之血
"The blood of our own."
记录者的血
Men of letters blood.
传人的血
Legacy blood.
我的血
My blood.
记得我们第一次见时你对我说了什么吗
Remember what you said to me when we first met?
说这地方纯粹什么的
About the purity of this place?
迪恩 走慢点
Dean, slow down.
迪恩 站住
Dean, stop.
听
Listen.
这个声音
This?
在这里 你不用去找麻烦
This place, you don't have to go looking for a fight.
你只需静静地等上一会儿
All you have to is be still for one moment,
麻烦就找上门了
and that fight will come to you.
那就是你在这里的原因 迪恩
That's why you're here, Dean.
那就是你渴望的纯粹
That's the purity you crave …
不用背负任何后果的杀戮
killing with no consequence.
不 本尼 我不想再打下去了
No, Benny, I don't wanna fight anymore.
我已经厌倦打斗了
I'm tired of fightin'.
但血印没有
The mark ain't.
那么…你既不能走
So…can't leave.
但也不想留下来
Don't wanna stay.
这下有点麻烦了 是不是
Bit of a bind, ain't it?
好消息是 总有第三条路可选
Good thing there's always a third way out.
你不能说自己从没想过吧
You can't say you haven't been thinking about it.
那是不可能的 永远不会
That ain't gonna happen, ever.
拜托 迪恩
Come on, Dean.
我知道你明白的
I know you can see it.
那种纯粹 那种荣耀
The purity, the honor.
那没什么荣耀可言
There's no honor in that.
怎么 你就干等着被血印重新控制住吗
What, you just wanna wait for the mark to reclaim you?
回到人间 在战斗中牺牲 然后呢
Go out swinging, die topside, then what?
也许还要误伤几个人类
Maybe kill a few humans?
害死小卡 害死你弟弟
Kill Cass? Kill your brother?
是啊 那可真是荣耀至极啊
Yeah, that's mighty honorable!
闭嘴
Shut up!
对不起 我忘了…
Oh, I-I'm sorry. I forgot…
你的计划
about your plan.
你打算让萨姆和小卡干掉你
You gonna get Sam and Cass to put you down?
你真觉得他俩会遵守约定吗 别逗了
You really think they're gonna keep that agreement? Come on.
迪恩 就算他俩照做了
Dean, let's say they do.
你觉得他俩还能从那件事里缓过来吗
Do you think they will ever recover from that?
那会毁了他们的
It will ruin them.
你的这个备用计划
This little backup plan of yours,
我知道你想了好一阵了
I know you've been thinking about it for a time.
我知道你因此痛不欲生
I know it's been gnawin' at you.
你不能把那苦差事留给他们
You can't leave that job to them.
你说得对
You're right.
在现实里 你睡着了
Out there? You're sleeping.
你在这里做出正确的决定
You make the right choice in here,
你就能长睡不醒了
you'll sleep forever,
再也不会伤害到任何人了
and you won't ever hurt anyone ever again.
别人不需要知道 迪恩
No one needs to know, Dean.
在炼狱里发生的一切 只会留在炼狱
What happens in purgatory, stays in purgatory.
你怎么知道这样能起作用
How do you know this will work?
我不知道
I don't.
起作用了
It's working.
我的确喜欢这里
I always did love it here.
在这里结束也不差 是吧
It's as good a place as any to call it a day, huh?
慢点
Slow down.
好的
Right. Okay.
不不不
No, no, no.
它想要更多的血 萨姆
It wants more, Sam.
它要你全部的血
It wants it all.
法典…
The codex…
通向解决办法的途径
path to the cure.
就在里面
It's in there.
假如它还要 我就满足它
If it wants more, it'll get more.
我愿意动手
I'd do it.
假如我真的必须动手
If I really had to,
我会的
I would.
但是真正的本尼
But the real Benny.
绝不会让我那么做
would never let me.
我们已经讨论过那个了 伙计
We already covered that, chief.
不是我让你这么做
It's not me.
你知道还有什么会阻止我吗
You know what else won't let me?
我胳膊上的这玩意
This thing on my arm.
不管怎样 这个血印…
For better or worse, the mark…
希望我活着
it wants me alive.
谢了 兄弟
Thanks, pal,
但还是算了
But no thanks.
要打开了 萨姆
It's opening, Sammy!
快成功了
It's nearly there!
萨姆
Sam!
萨姆 不管你看到的是什么 都是假的
Sammy, whatever you're seeing, it's … it's a trick.
好吗 不是真的
Okay? It's not real!
- 迪恩 - 嗯
- Dean? - Yeah.
不不
No. No.
别过来
Get away from me!
不 不要 不要
No, don't! Don't!
这是唯一的办法
It's the only way.
- 它需要传人的血 - 不
- It needs legacy blood… - No.
足以让人送命的量
Enough to take a life.
好吧
Yeah, well…
不非得来自一个人 不是吗
It doesn't have to come from just one legacy, does it?
如果它需要更多的血 就拿我的吧
It needs more blood, it can have mine.
好吧
Oh, well.
有点过头了吧
Overkill, don't you think?
我们打破了诅咒
I mean, we broke the spell.
箱子如今只是个箱子了
The box is just a box.
现在只是废弃金属了
Well, now it's scrap metal.
你还好吗
You okay?
很好
Yeah, I'm great.
可以出发了吗
You road ready?
我没事的
I'll be fine.
这说明了点问题 不是吗
That says something, doesn't it?
维特把我们分开
Werther splits us up in there.
不到一小时 我们就都濒临死亡了
Within an hour, we're both on the brink of death?
很抱歉昨天单独行动了
Sorry about yesterday, going rogue on you like that.
你知道吗 迪恩 别道歉
You know what, Dean? Don't apologize. I…
我觉得我俩扯平了
I think that makes us even.
宇宙想要告诉我们
The universe is trying to tell us something.
我们都早该知道的道理
we both should already know.
我们在一起比分开要强大
We're stronger together than apart.
什么东西那么有价值
Now what could possibly be so valuable.
需要这么邪恶的咒语来保护
that it takes a spell that nasty to protect it, huh?
不知道
No idea.
不管是什么
Whatever it is,
我们要确保它的安全
we'll keep it safe.
你好啊 牛仔
Well, hello, cowboy.
你拿到了
Oh, you've got it!
够了吗
Is it enough?
什么
To what?
翻译书
To translate the book.
找到治愈血印的办法
Find a cure for the mark.
是啊
Oh, aye.
很好
Good.
什么…
Wh…
这是什么意思
What in the hell is this?!
保险
Insurance.
舒服吗
Comfortable?
我们达成了协议的 巨人
We had an agreement, giant.
协议依旧
The agreement stands.
你要破解《诅咒之书》
You will decrypt The Book of The Damned.
为我哥哥找到治愈办法
and find me a cure for my brother.
这是你从书里唯一能得到的东西
And that is all you will get from the book.
我会烧了那本书 杀死克劳力
I'll burn the book, then I'll kill Crowley.
但在那之前
But until then…
我是你的奴隶吗
I'm your slave?
你不能把我就这么丢在这里
You can't … you can't just leave me here.
你想出去吗 快点干活儿吧
You wanna out? Hurry up. Get to work.
你个大坏蛋
You big bampot!